RAHUL R KALAL

Bangalore India | 8217367345 | rahulkalal676@gmail.com

[IMMEDIATE JOINER]

SUMMARY

Full stack developer arround **1 years of experience** in designing and developing effective to products of Bank management Proven ability to deliver world class projecis that drive operational efficiency, enhance customer experience and exceed the business

objectives

Organized and disciplined professional with Strong Problem solving skill dedicated to excellence drive for win win situations

SKILLS

- SDLC
- Fluent in Java, Spring boot,Reactjs, HTML5,css, javascript,sdlc,git,ci-cd etc
- Scrum
- · Code Reviews
- Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC)

- · Test Planning and QA
- · Database Management
- · Code Development
- MvSQL
- API Design

EXPERIENCE

01/2022 - 01/2023

Software Engineer 1

Paycraft solution Pvt Ltd — Mumbai , India

- Analyzed user requirements to develop software solutions and created technical specifications.
- Developed, tested, debugged and documented software programs using Java, Javascript and HTML and CSS.
- Conducted unit tests on code modules to verify accuracy and functionality of program logic.
- Assisted junior developers in understanding complex coding concepts and debugging errors.

10/2021 - 01/2022

Trainee

Jspider — Bangalore , India

Conducted research on best practices in employee training procedures.

04/2021 - 09/2021

Mobile Application Developer Intern

The Spark foundation

 Resolved technical Issues related to mobile application development and deployment processes.

02/2021 - 04/2021

Web Developer Intern

TechnoSoft — Tumkur, India

- · Developed web applications using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Tested and debugged code for compatibility across multiple browsers.
- Collaborated with other developers to enhance the user experience of websites.

EDUCATION

2017-2021 -

B.E: Computer Science And Engineering VTU Bangalore - 7.14/10